[Music]
[Música]
Good morning family I hope you are
buenos días familia espero que estéis
very well I send a huge hug 8 to
muy bien mando un abrazo enorme 8 de
comment on the latest news about
comentar la última noticia que hay sobre
the oops case this is very important
el caso del oops esto es muy importante
and it is quite strong and could
y es bastante fuerte y podría dar un
overturn the information we have
vuelco a la información que tenemos
to this day it was very complicated to
hasta el día de hoy era muy complicado
prove the bribery that possibly
probar el cohecho que posiblemente haya
occurred in this case by
sucedido en este caso por parte de
Gustavo Gonzalez paying some money
gustavo gonzález pagándole algún dinero
in exchange to the police officer or officers
a cambio al policía oa los policías
because in the last car to which we have had
porque en el último auto al que hemos
access there are three police officers
tenido acceso hay tres policías
involved and this is a pleasant surprise we do
implicados y esto es una grata sorpresa
not know what role each one would have
no sabemos qué papel tendría cada uno
but well I imagine that obviously it
pero bueno me imagino que evidentemente
will be the role of the role of getting
pues será el papel del papel de meterse
into the files and looking to see what
en los ficheros y mirar a ver qué es lo
was there not from the famous ones no the move
que había no de los famosos no la movida
is that it is going to be investigated and
es que se va a investigar y se va a
the instruction of the case is going to be extended for six
alargar la instrucción del caso seis
more months with this we will surely
meses más con esto ya seguramente nos
get into it in 2023 less surely we will
metamos en 2023 menos seguro nos
get into it in 2023 and it is that they want to
meteremos en 2023 y es que quieren
investigate a little more into the issue of the
indagar un poco más en el tema de las
payrolls and the payments of Gustavo Gonzalez
nóminas y los pagos de gustavo gonzález
because we could  to be talking
porque podríamos estar hablando
calmly about a crime of bribery and it's
tranquilamente de un delito de cohecho y
that well it has seemed very strange to all of us
es que bueno a todos nos ha resultado
that this policeman for simple
muy raro que este policía por simple
love of art' and his colleagues began to
amor al arte' y sus colegas se pusieran
do this thing not this crime as
a hacer esta cosa no este delito tan
serious as getting into
gordo como meterse en las fichas
people's police files passing the
policiales de la gente pasarle la
information to the people from Sálvame so that
información a los de sálvame para que
the people from Sálvame would start publishing it
los de sálvame se pusieran a publicarla
on their program no
en su programa no
no
no nadie se cree que esto lo hicieron
nobody believes that they did this for free and the judge is not worth it either the judge who is handling the case has asked the tax agency for all the possible information from the television factory all the invoices and the thing is that there are some very strange months in
y es que hay unos meses muy extraños en
which Gustavo González would have gone
los que gustavo gonzález habría pasado
from earning three thousand euros a month
de cobrar tres mil euros al mes
pay attention to 20 thousand and almost nothing the jump from
atención a 20 mil y casi na el salto de
three thousand euros a month to twenty thousand
tres mil euros al mes a veinte mil
then of course there we surely have
entonces claro ahí seguramente tengamos
the possible payment that Gustavo would have made to
el posible pago que gustavo le haría a
his friends not to the police
sus amiguitos no a los policías
remembered of course that it is very
recordaron por supuesto que es muy
important that they have charged the
importante que hayan imputado a los
directors and the owners of the
directores y a los dueños de la fábrica
television factory as a physical person okay
de la tele como persona física vale
Oscar
oscar
Cornejo and Adrian Madrid are  accused
cornejo y adrián madrid están imputados
as individuals, not as
como personas físicas ya no como
legal entities of the
personas jurídicas de la farga de la
television gang, but rather they are in a big
tele sino que están metidos en un buen
mess, and the fact is that these people believe they are unpunished,
lío y es que esta gente se creen impunes
they believe they are above the law, and doing
se creen por lo alto de la ley y hacer
this is nonsense, in other words,
esto es una burrada o sea que se
publishing exclusives on celebrity gossip shows
publiquen en programas del corazón
based on the fact that a police officer
exclusivas basadas en que un policía se
has entered the data file and the
ha metido en la ficha de datos y en las
police files of people where there are
fichas policiales de la gente donde hay
videos, photos, calls from all sorts of
videos fotos atestados llamadas de todo
super intimate people, it's outrageous, the
super íntimo de los famosos es de traca
family will be reading it, I will keep you
familia se estará leyendo os mantendré
informed, I send you a huge hug.
informados os mando un abrazo enorme
[Music]
[Música]